Welcome to Jhal Ki Taisi Service Channel,
in this video I will tell you how
you can subscribe to ICICI Debit Card, so
for this subscribe,
as you know, share subscribe in the box from your side, then
open this portal
and after that log in,
I have logged in here, the portal,
so here you are seeing first of all that
our portal has opened,
so you have to go to insurance,
after going to insurance you
can see here motor third party insurance,
in this you will
click on ICICI Lombard JCL Motor Third Party, you will see that
ICC chief gives very good service
for insurance, so here you can see
motor and health, two wheeler, car,
PC, pet, so this diabetes patient and
what you have to do is to invest in the policy,
so to invest you have to do it here, so
here we are
that get full court of it,
as you can see here this
page of ours will open, okay, third party
standalone audio policy, okay if you want to do
this third party standalone then  If you want to do that
policy then you have to do this, click on subscribe, then you will
enter the registration number of the vehicle, the registration number will be given
here, the appointed registration age,
you yourself have to fill in the new model, the company's
car, then the ex-showroom price, Raghava, show here
that this much price is being charged for your vehicle,
then you have to enter customer state,
policy date etc., the policy type is
dal, it is a product that has been made for a short period,
okay, so for how many years do you have to insure all these things, for
one, two, three years,
okay, I will
enter the manufacturing date of the vehicle,
if you have done the republic renewal earlier, the
balance is bad or else all the
details are there, then you will enter the registration type, company,
additionally you need appointed village, you are getting so
angry, then if
we do a maximum of 800 something, then
we will do it by paying from CSC wallet,
we will
give it to the customs, the RDX that will come out in the blast, you mean what I meant to
say was how does this happen, hatred,
these are all the things, you can do it, so thank
you, so much take care transaction, these are all the
things, thank you